shopbychoice.com 2015-12-30

# Privacy Policy - shopbychoice.com

### Understanding Registration

shopbychoice.com' understands your privacy. You are suggested to acquaint the privacy policy and understand it carefully. Privacy policy avails you the precise manner by which your precious information is captured and used by us. This section discloses that how your information is gathered from you and treated by us. Although this portion comprises of detailed list of policies that you must read before going further. As we expect that you should know all our services and practices followed by us and that may help you in taking profound decision. 

By **understanding registration** policy we believe that you agree to our disclosure and use of personal information as per privacy norms.

### Honor Your Privacy

We here at 'shopbychoice.com', boastfully assure you to protect all your confidential data. We honor your trust and faith on us. We assure you that you can confidently count on our services and after winning your trust you will definitely recommend us to your family and friends. Before that do read our policy procedure that how your precious information is treated by us to provide you the maximum use and resulting the best output.

### We Wish Users To

  * **1.** Do feel free and comfortable using our website.
  * **2.** Feel secure and trust on us while submitting and sharing the confidential information.
  * **3.** Consent while browser the collection of data.

### Privacy Assured

We assure you that your confidential information will not be revealed, rent, shared or sold to the third party (as per our privacy norms) without your assent. We may share/use your personal information to the authorized third party to avail the services which are providers on our portals.

Timely, we may disclose the statistical information about our visitors and website in general including aggregate number of visitors, type and numbers of services and goods purchased etc. your privacy is our priority.

### Gathering Information

We gather data by the information you mention in the registration form and we know by keeping a track of liking and the services provided by us when visiting our site and other possible accessible sites. we gather additional information when you participate in any competition and promotions presented by our site.We also gather information when you write comments, feedback and accomplish the profile forms. We only gather such information which is relevant and essential to us that can be further help to your in availing the services present on the website.

### Anonymous Information

We can retrieve and gather anonymous information by logs generated via web server that may include cookies from which we can gain information like your computer identification number etc. from:

  * **1.** Cookies that is stored on your hard disk.
  * **2.** Assigned IP address of your system
  * **3.** Even from the domain server, from where you access our services.

### Personal Identification

We may also gather information about you like:

  * Your first and last name
  * Postal/ ZIP code
  * Contact details including your mobile number, landline numbers etc.

We use these information internally to:

  * Contact you for survey of our site and services.
  * Questionnaires for improvement in any existing or new launched product.
  * Send you promotional material for our contest, advertisements and sponsors.

### Declaration Regarding Your Information

We will not exploit your confidential data for any malicious purpose; we will merely use it for completing our transaction with you.

We declare that your personal information including your personal identification will not be disclose, share, sell, reveal, rent to any third party until:

  * Your consent/agreement.
  * You requested for any product and services.
  * To assist in preventing, investigating and taking measureable actions regarding any illegal or unlawful actions and activities like suspected fraud, threat against security and safety and violations of **shopbychoice.com** terms of use and conditions.
  * Other situations like court orders, order/request for legal authorities, complaint with subpoenas etc.

### Security

We assure that we will protect and maintain security against the misuse, alteration and misuse of you confidential information and keep all under our control. We take measureable steps for your data security. No illegal and unauthorized acts can be done while using our site.

No liability for your information disclosure due error in transmission and unauthorized party in between.

### Policy Update

We have complete right to update and amend this policy at anytime. Changes made shall be informed immediately on the website.

### Your Agreement

This agreement consents that while using this site you agree to the collection and information disclosure by you when using this site. If there are any changes/updates made to this privacy policy we will let you know by posting on our web page. Now you agree with what information we use and how we use your information and under what circumstance we disclose it.
